---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=5305f41e696d24a05573d0a59e56e6ca; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A
        universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these
        is NOT a playable character in the 2016 video game Overwatch?","correct_answer":"Invoker","incorrect_answers":["Mercy","Winston","Zenyatta"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which movie includes
        a giant bunny-like spirit who has magic powers including growing trees?","correct_answer":"My
        Neighbor Totoro","incorrect_answers":["Hop","Rise of the Guardians","Alice
        in Wonderland"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        was Socrates executed?","correct_answer":"Poison","incorrect_answers":["Decapitation","Firing
        squad","Crucifixion "]},{"category":"Politics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        was the 45th President of the United States?","correct_answer":"Donald Trump","incorrect_answers":["Barack
        Obama","Bill Clinton","George Bush"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Cartoon
        & Animations","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is Everest&#039;s
        favorite food in the Nickelodeon\/Nick Jr. series &quot;PAW Patrol&quot;?","correct_answer":"Liver","incorrect_answers":["Chicken","Steak","Caribou"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        year did World War I begin?","correct_answer":"1914","incorrect_answers":["1905","1919","1925"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        boxer was banned for taking a bite out of Evander Holyfield&#039;s ear in
        1997?","correct_answer":"Mike Tyson","incorrect_answers":["Roy Jones Jr.","Evander
        Holyfield","Lennox Lewis"]},{"category":"Art","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        painting was not made by Vincent Van Gogh?","correct_answer":"The Ninth Wave","incorrect_answers":["Caf&eacute;
        Terrace at Night","Bedroom In Arles","Starry Night"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game
        &quot;Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon&quot;, what is the central protagonist&#039;s
        name?","correct_answer":"Marth","incorrect_answers":["Roy","Eliwood","Robin"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:39:08 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
